{
	"test": [
		{
			"number": 1,
			"question": "Under the US Constitution, which body has the sole authority to declare war?",
			"graphic": "noone",
			"answers": [
				"The President",
				"The U.S. Congress",
				"The Secretary of Defense",
				"The chairman of the Joint Chiefs of Staff"
			],
			"answer": "The U.S. Congress"
		},
		{
			"number": 2,
			"question": "Given the above information, which of the following statements is the most logical conclusion?",
			"graphic": "Social_Quiz_2_1",
			"answers": [
				"A higher unemployment rate leads to more tax revenue",
				"A lower unemployment rate leads to more tax revenue",
				"There is no relationship between unemployment and tax revenue",
				"A higher unemployment rate leads to more tax fraud"
			],
			"answer": "A lower unemployment rate leads to more tax revenue"
		},
		{
			"number": 3,
			"question": "Which of the following questions about NASA's budget would be the most difficult to answer?",
			"graphic": "noone",
			"answers": [
				"How does NASA spend its money?",
				"Does the United States spend too much money on space exploration?",
				"How much of an increase did NASA receive over last year's budget?",
				"How much do we spend on astronaut training annually?"
			],
			"answer": "Does the United States spend too much money on space exploration?"
		},
		{
			"number": 4,
			"question": "What was the primary goal of the Confederacy in fighting the Civil War?",
			"graphic": "Social_Quiz_2_2",
			"answers": [
				"To rejoin the United States",
				"To take control of the federal government of the United States",
				"To remain an independent country where slavery was permitted",
				"To wipe out the Union and destroy the northern states"
			],
			"answer": "To remain an independent country where slavery was permitted"
		},
		{
			"number": 5,
			"question": "What is the most likely reason that the Confederate States of America won several major battles early in the Civil War?",
			"graphic": "Social_Quiz_2_2",
			"answers": [
				"The Confederacy had a great supply line to fortify their troops with guns and ammunition.",
				"The Confederacy had a much larger army.",
				"The Confederacy had superior military generals who outmaneuvered the Union troops.",
				"The Confederacy produced more food."
			],
			"answer": "The Confederacy had superior military generals who outmaneuvered the Union troops."
		},
		{
			"number": 6,
			"question": "What would be the best title for the chart?",
			"graphic": "Social_Quiz_2_2",
			"answers": [
				"Comparing the advantages and disadvantages of the Union and Confederacy",
				"Comparison of military supplies of the Union and Confederacy armies",
				"Understanding why the Union won the Civil War",
				"Understanding the advantages the Confederacy had over the Union"
			],
			"answer": "Comparing the advantages and disadvantages of the Union and Confederacy"
		},
		{
			"number": 7,
			"question": "Which of the following statements from this passage is an opinion and not a fact?",
			"graphic": "Social_Quiz_2_3",
			"answers": [
				"'While each of Florida's 27 electoral delegates represents almost 480,000 eligible voters,\n each of the three delegates from Wyoming represents only 135,000 eligible voters.'",
				"'That makes a voter casting a presidential ballot in Wyoming three and a half times more\n influential than a voter in Florida.'",
				"'This system, along with the winner-take-all practice used to allocate most states'\n electoral votes, creates the potential for an absurd outcome.'",
				"The presidency could be won with just 22 percent of the electorate's support, only 16 percent\n of the entire population's."
			],
			"answer": "'This system, along with the winner-take-all practice used to allocate most states'\n electoral votes, creates the potential for an absurd outcome.'"
		},
		{
			"number": 8,
			"question": "Which of the following statements is a logical inference based upon evidence from the passage?",
			"graphic": "Social_Quiz_2_4",
			"answers": [
				"President Wilson does not want the US to retaliate against the Germans.",
				"President Wilson believes that the US should retaliate against the Germans regardless of what other countries decide.",
				"President Wilson believes fear and anger should stir American support for war against Germany.",
				"President Wilson wants to wait and see how other nations respond to the German attacks before declaring war."
			],
			"answer": "President Wilson believes that the US should retaliate against the Germans regardless of what other countries decide."
		},
		{
			"number": 9,
			"question": "The 'right to bear arms' is granted by which amendment of the United States Constitution?",
			"graphic": "Social_Quiz_2_5",
			"answers": [
				"First Amendment",
				"Second Amendment",
				"Fifth Amendment",
				"Second Amendment"
			],
			"answer": "Second Amendment"
		},
		{
			"number": 10,
			"question": "According to the chart, which of the following states does not require a mental health background check to purchase a firearm?",
			"graphic": "Social_Quiz_2_5",
			"answers": ["California", "Texas", "Florida", "Illinois"],
			"answer": "California"
		}
	]
}
